<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<metadata xml:lang="he">
  <Esri>
    <CreaDate>20251210</CreaDate>
    <CreaTime>21090800</CreaTime>
    <ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat>
    <SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce>
  </Esri>
  <dataIdInfo>
    <idCitation>
      <resTitle>אשפי בנק"ל</resTitle>
    </idCitation>
    <idAbs>&lt;P&gt;The Israeli National Cadaster Database is one of the state's most critical repositories of land and property information. To ensure its reliability and accuracy, a systematically organized collection of task items has been developed. These tasks form the core of ongoing efforts to update, maintain, and refine the cadaster, keeping it as the central reference for land ownership, boundaries, and registration.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Each task is a clearly defined unit of work, associated with structured actions and procedures. These may include verifying parcel boundaries, cross-referencing survey data, updating ownership records, reconciling historical maps with modern measurements, or correcting errors that could compromise database accuracy. Consistent execution ensures that each action contributes to the integrity of the overall cadastral system.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Systematic execution is essential. Land information supports property registration, taxation, urban planning, infrastructure, and environmental management. An outdated or inconsistent cadaster could cause disputes, inefficiencies, or legal uncertainty. Thus, all tasks are carried out with precision and attention to detail.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Procedures are documented, validated, and reviewed to ensure transparency and traceability. This maintains stakeholder trust—from government agencies to surveyors and developers—and ensures the cadaster supports accurate land management, efficient resource allocation, and secure land registration.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P /&gt;&lt;P&gt;In essence, these task items sustain the legal and administrative infrastructure underpinning land ownership in Israel. Through disciplined execution, the cadaster remains a vital instrument for governance, economic development, and public trust.&lt;/P&gt;</idAbs>
    <idPurp></idPurp>
    <searchKeys>
      <keyword>Tasks</keyword>
      <keyword>אשפי בנק"ל</keyword>
    </searchKeys>
  </dataIdInfo>
</metadata>